Our palace is not working overtime today
本宫今天不加班
Episode I
第一集
This is Sister Li's file
这个是李姐的文件
Super copied documents
超超的复印文件
Sister Jing's Sister Jing's
静姐的 静姐的
Have you eaten yet
吃饭了吗
Don't be too tired at the beginning of work
刚开始上班别太累
Take Good Care of Yourself
好好照顾自己
Okay, Dad, I'm going to sleep.
好的 爸 我这就睡了
He's Mingyue
何氏明月
Wen Wan Shu De
温婉淑德
Elegant and dignified
娴雅端庄
Queen He Queen He
何皇后 着册封为后
For the Mother of the World
为天下之母仪
The Emperor
皇上
Xu Gonggong
许公公
A little palace maid at the beginning
当初的一个小宫女
Quiet concubine Quiet concubine
静嫔 居然爬到我们头上来了
I knew this earlier
早知如此
When she knelt down and begged for mercy
当初她跪地求饶时
I should have taken care of her
我就该解决她
How could the emperor be blinded by her
皇上怎么就被她
I'm obsessed
迷了心窍呀
Zhao Bin Zhao Bin
赵嫔 论家世 论才貌
How can she compare with Wei Guifei
她哪点比得上魏贵妃
Wei Guifei Wei Guifei
魏贵妃 何明月
The Emperor spoils you now
皇上现在宠你
And you can guarantee
你又能保证
How long is this love
这份宠爱多久呢
Small pine nuts
小松子呢
Reply to the mother's words
回娘娘的话
Little Songzi father-in-law has something to do temporarily
小松子公公临时有事
Let me help you
我来扶您吧
This little maid is too courageous
这小宫女胆子也太大了
Didn't she rely on this trick at the beginning?
当初她不也是靠的这招
Seducing the Emperor
勾引的皇上吗
Come
来人
Called the Imperial Doctor
叫太医
Xuanmaoyi Quick Xuanmaoyi
宣太医 快宣太医
Emperor
皇上
Now it's my canonization
现在是我的册封大典
How about first
不如先
The little beauty fainted
小美人都晕倒了
Is the ceremony important or human life important?
大典重要还是人命重要
Queen
皇后
I didn't expect
我没想到
You're a selfish man
你是个自私自利的人
How can you be a mother of the world like this?
你这样怎么母仪天下
I was so disappointed by this
这事让我太失望了
What about the imperial doctor
太医呢
What is Xiao Xuzi doing in a daze
小许子愣着干吗
It's not called imperial medicine yet
还不叫太医
The emperor has sent for it
皇上 已经派人去叫了
Even if I became a queen
纵使我成了皇后
And he's still
他也依旧是
See one and love one
见一个爱一个
My whole life
我这一生
After all, it was a wrong payment
终究是错付了
Poison wine
鸩酒
White silk
白绫
Could the emperor have
皇上难道
Because of the event of the Great Ceremony of the Dynasty
因为当朝大典的事情
To die
就要赐死
I am the empress of the dynasty
我这个当朝皇后
Sleeping soundly
睡得香吗
Liu Jing
刘静
Quiet concubine
静嫔
Liu Jing Liu Jing
刘静 大清都亡了多少年了
Still here
还在这儿
What are you daydreaming about
做什么白日梦呢
Go
去
I took this document for a photocopy
把这文件拿去复印了
What kind of dream did this palace have
本宫这是做的什么梦
He Jiaojiao, you are quite deep in the play
何皎皎 你入戏还挺深
There's this drama queen time
有这个戏精时间
Hurry up and go
还不赶紧去
I took the document and made a copy
把文件拿去复印了
You're just a quiet concubine
你区区一个静嫔
You dare to shout at me
都敢对我呼来喝去的了
He Jiaojiao, are you crazy?
何皎皎 你是不是疯了
Believe or not this palace
信不信本宫
Put you in the cold
把你打入冷宫
You're a little intern
你一个小小的实习生
Early in the morning here
大清早在这
What the hell is going on
发什么疯啊
Want to dry and don't want to roll
想干干 不想干滚
Sister Jing, are you all right
静姐 你没事吧
You calm down first
你先消消气
He Jiaojiao
何皎皎
Why don't you apologize to Sister Jing?
还不赶紧给静姐道歉
Isn't this a dream
难道这不是梦
And at this point my identity
而且此时我的身份
Lower than a quiet concubine
比静嫔还低
Sister Jing, I'm kidding
静姐 我开玩笑呢
That copy, right?
那个 复印是吧
I'm going
我这就去
Three, please
三份啊 谢谢
And this
还有这个
People here are really lazy
这的人可真会偷懒
Even the strokes are simplified
连笔画都给简化了
Complex
复
Seal
印
Chamber
室
How to use it?
到底怎么用啊
Du Xiaosong.
杜小松
Du Gonggong
杜公公
Du Xiaosong. Du Xiaosong.
杜小松 小松
What are you doing here
你怎么在这儿啊
You are;
你是
That crazy, grumpy intern
那个疯狂暴躁实习生
Why, why are you looking at me like that
干嘛 干嘛这么看着我
This hair
这头发
I'm sorry I'm sorry
对不起 对不起 对不起
This is a new skirt that I just bought
这是人家刚买的新裙裙
Zhao Ting. Zhao Ting.
赵婷 你们太讨厌了
Zhao Bin
赵嫔
Zhao Ting.
赵婷
What to do
怎么办
I'm sorry
对不起
I didn't mean to
我不是故意的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
对不起 我不是故意的
The minions knew they were wrong
奴才知错了
The minions don't dare anymore
奴才再也不敢了
This is the palace
这可是本宫
For the Queen Mother's birthday banquet
为了太后寿宴
Clothes specially tailored by the embroidery workshop
特意让绣坊裁制的衣服
Just like this, you're a little eunuch
就这样被你一个小太监
Get dirty
给弄脏了
Somebody drag it down
来人 拖下去
Break his hand for me
把他手给我打断
Intern
实习生
You don't have eyes
你没长眼睛
To see someone pass by
看到有人经过
You're still there
你还杵在那
You are wood;
你是木头
I help you
我帮你
Don't you touch me
你别碰我
Just your shitty salary
就你那点破工资
Can you afford my skirt
你赔得起我裙子吗
The skirt is really nice
裙子确实挺好看的
Too bad
可惜了
That's a good thing you said
你这话说得倒是不错
That
那
Dry cleaning fee
干洗费
Give it to me
给我吧
Wait a minute
等一下
How can I see
我怎么看见
You hit him
是你撞的他呢
Co-authored by two interns
合着是两个实习生
Hold together
一起抱团
To bully me as a regular employee
来欺负我这个正式员工
You think
你觉得
Am I afraid of you
我会怕你们吗
Anyway, today's skirt
总之 今天这条裙子
Someone must be responsible
必须有人负责
Empress
娘娘
Please spare him
请您饶了他吧
What the hell are you
你又是个什么东西
Do you have a word for this round
这轮得到你说话吗
The maidservant asked you to spare him
娘娘 奴婢让您饶了他
It's for your own good
是为了您好
Today is the Queen Mother's birthday feast
今天可是太后的生辰宴
The Queen Mother has worshiped Buddha for many years
太后礼佛多年
If I saw blood today
要是在今天见了血
Not very well, I'm afraid
恐怕不太好吧
There is some truth to what you say
你说得倒是有几分道理
But my clothes
但我这衣裳
Empress
娘娘
A slave has a family trade
奴婢有个家传的手艺
Let the maidservant give you a try
不如让奴婢给您试试
Look, my lady
娘娘 您看
It's not too bad
倒也还凑合
It's getting late
时间不早了
This palace is going to the Palace of Compassion and Ning
本宫要去慈宁宫了
Get out of the way
让开
This is a slave
这才是一个奴婢
The way it should be
该有的样子
But you
可是你们
Crash the master first
先冲撞本主子在先
Don't think that some little trick
别以为一些小把戏
You can cancel out
就可以抵消
If you are really responsible
真要负责的话
It's not his turn
也轮不到他吧
What do you mean
你什么意思啊
You;
你
Look
看
Code of Practice for the Management of Copy Rooms Article 3
复印室管理守则第三条
Prohibition of food
禁止将食品
Beverages
饮料
Beverages brought in
饮料带入
Lest cause
以免造成
Machine
机器
Machine breakage
机器破坏
What is this
这是什么呀
Don't take this thing
你少拿这个东西
To scare me
来吓唬我
Up and down the company
全公司上上下下
People who eat and drink here
在这吃吃喝喝的人
Too much to go
多了去了
I'm not the only one
又不止我一个
Is it
是吗
It really seems like you're the only one
好像确实只有你一个
Look what I'm doing
看我干嘛
Remember a sentence
记住一句话
Be forgiven and forgive
得饶人处且饶人
Why not do this today
不如今天这事
Just let it go
就这么算了吧
He Jiaojiao, right?
何皎皎是吧
I remember you
我记住你了
Heaven reaps the wicked
恶人自有天收
If the sky doesn't accept it, I will accept it
天不收我收
Sister Mingyue, what do you mean
明月姐 你的意思是
I put honey on her
我给她涂的是蜂蜜
Today is the Queen Mother's birthday
今天是太后的寿辰
I see what she should do
我看她该怎么办
Five four three two one
五 四 三 二 一
He Mingyue
何明月
You are too powerful
你也太厉害了吧
If it hadn't been for you
刚才要不是你
I'm really going to lose her money
我真的准备赔她钱了呢
Don't be afraid of her
别怕她
Zhao Pin, this man
赵嫔这个人啊
It is to bully the weak and fear the hard
就是欺软怕硬
In fact, it is very vulnerable
其实根本不堪一击
Zhao Bin
赵 嫔
This
这
Where is this accent
这是哪个地方的口音啊
Zhao Ting
赵 婷
By the way, what am I supposed to call you
对了 我该怎么叫你啊
Empress
娘娘啊
Joking
开玩笑的
You just call me
你就叫我
Sister Jiaojiao
皎皎姐吧
We're not sure
咱们俩指不定
Who is bigger than the other
谁比谁大呢
Whoa, whoa
小屁孩 让你叫你就叫
Okay, Sister Jiaojiao
好吧 皎皎姐
Right
对了
I have a question for you
我有个问题想问你
This is it
就是这个
How to use the photocopier
复印机到底怎么用啊
Cool
酷
You mean our company is great
你是说我们公司很厉害
Right
对啊
Since our new president, Li Su
自从咱们的新总裁李溯
After taking office
上任之后吧
In just a few years
短短几年时间
The size of the company;
公司的规模
Are expanded several times
都扩大好几倍呢
This Mr. Li
这个李总啊
Not only strong working ability
不仅工作能力强
And young, handsome and rich
而且年轻帅气又多金
Executive meeting in five minutes
五分钟后召开高管会议
Two p.m.
下午两点
Meeting on the Grand Mang Project
关于大芒计划的会议
Particularly important
特别重要
President
总裁
It is the top level of this company.
就是这个公司最顶层呗
All the powers of life and death
所有的生杀大权
It's all in his hands
都在他的手上
Screenwriter, you really dare to write
编剧你真是挺敢写的
Now that it's all over again
既然都重来了
You think I'm gonna be honest
你以为我会老老实实
Follow the script
按照剧本走么
Screenwriter, you're naive
编剧 你太天真了
I want to have a good time
我偏要活个痛快
Sister, what are you doing
姐 你干嘛呢
Where were we?
我们说到哪了
Yes, set it a small goal first
对 先定它个小目标
Be a company president for fun
当个公司总裁玩玩吧
I don't have a fever
也没发烧啊
You're still stupid
你还是傻傻的
Cute
真可爱
Let's go
走吧
Why is there no one?
怎么没人啊
President Mr. Li
总裁 李总
It's the legend
就是那个传奇人物
Let me see
我看看
Excuse me, don't get in the way
借过一下 不要挡路
Let me borrow it
借过一下
I didn't expect
我没想到
You're a selfish man
你是个自私自利的人
This dead man
这个死男人
Still hooking up around now
现在还在四处勾搭
Do it if it comes
既来之 则干之
You forced me
是你逼我的
Everything is a mystery Everything is a mystery
♪一切是个谜 无厘头 皇后也从头实习♪
Fingering and being careful Fingering and being careful
♪指指点点 小心翼翼 职场也变宫心计♪
It's all about this and that It's all about this and that
♪就这点那题 请你照顾好你自己♪
The palace gets used to it in a second
♪本宫一秒就适应♪
You don't have to be polite You don't have to be polite
♪你们不必表面客气 各自收好小心机♪
You have a good plan You have a good plan
♪你有张良计 而我自有我的过墙梯♪
Don't make me Buddhist Don't make me Buddhist
♪别把我佛系 容忍你的背后算计♪
Thought I was low
♪当成是我姿态低♪
Be yourself Be yourself
♪做好你自己 活的肆意 怎样来定义♪
Wait for me to counterattack in the wind
♪等我迎风逆袭♪